Gabriel Thome

Software Developer

eugabrielthome@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/gabrieltome/

Whatsapp: +55 (31) 99972-5228

Profile

Full-stack Developer with over 10 years, have experience in developing web apps and clean interfaces. Blending web development skills and good understanding of user experience to create digital products always seeking high convertion rate.

Knowledgement of Solidity, JavaScript, Node, React and Java

Solid understanding of Blockchain fundamentals, Ethereum EVM and API RESTful.

Experience in deployment of ERC-20, ERC-721, ERC-1155 tokens and have great familiarity with DeFi, Dapps, NFTs and DAOs.

My biggest soft skill is that I'm very self-taught and very adaptable, but I really enjoy good teamwork.

Specialties: Web applications, User Experience, Database Modeling and Blockchain environment.

Experience

Full-Stack Software Developer | Freelancer | 2010 – present

In web3dev DAO Solidity bootcamp, I build a collection of NFTs and their respective page to mint using web3 libraries.

In another web3 project I built a DAO, with participation NFTs, treasury tokens and governance tokens. (ERC-20, ERC-1155 and ERC-721).

Web3 stack: Solidity, Smart Contracts, Ethereum EVM, Hardhat, Truffle, Ganache, Alchemy, Thirdweb, OpenZeppelin.

Web2 stack: JavaScript, Java, Node, React, NoSQL, PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS Design skills: Sketch, Figma, Affinity

Product Design | Web Development | Alphon Tecnologia | 2020 – 2023

As a Web Developer and Digital Strategis, I work on the Alphon Technology to build and maintain her main websites and Landing Pages in high performance with scores > (A++) and 95%. Also have experience in PPC marketing with Facebook Ads and Google Ads.

 $\label{eq:maintenance} \textit{Main technologies: Figma, Webflow, HTML, CSS, Jav ascript, Google}$

Tag Manager

Android Developer | Protege | 04/2013 - 07/2013

PAGTAXI Project: Android app to track rides and payments with mifare cards. Main technologies: Java, Android, C

Mobile and Web Developer Intern | Unica Technology | 11/2010 - 03/2011

Main technologies: Java, Android, HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, jQuery.

Instructor of algorithms and programming logic | FACOMP 2010 – 2012

Support Analyst | Funorte | 01/2013 - 04/2013

Education

Faculdade de Computação (FACOMP) | 2008 - 2012

Bachelor's Degree in Information Systems

Pontifícia Universidade Católica de Minas Gerais (PUC-MG) | 2015 - 2017

Graduate in Web Application Development

Courses

2014 - Web Design Bruno Ávila - 60 Hrr

2011 - Agile with Scrum - 16 Hrs

2017 - Be MEAN - Mongo, Express, Angular, Node - webschool - 120 Hrs

2017 - JavaScript Course - Udemy

2018 - React - Origamid

2021 – Ethereum Solidity Course – Udemy

2021 - Yield Hacking / Yield Farmimg - 8h

2022 - Solidity Bootcamp - Codesign

2022 – Javascript DAO Bootcamp – Web3DAO

2022 - NFT with Javascript Bootcamp - Web3DAO

2023 -- Crypwitter - Decentralized Social Network

Conference/Organization

2022 ~ present – Web3dev DAO member

2021 ~ present – Developer DAO genesis member

2010/2011 ~ Campus Party Brasil

2011 ~ Instructor - Java SE Basic to Advanced Course

2012 ~ Instructor - Java / Android App Course

Publications

1. LISBOA, G. T. - Understanding the architecture of the Android Platform and the development of an application.. 2012, Minas Gerais, Brazil